<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on andrew-1234</title>
    <link>https://andrew-1234.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on andrew-1234</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 13:44:08 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrew-1234.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create a haplotype map using QGIS</title>
      <link>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/haplotype-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/haplotype-map/</guid>
      <description>This is how I made a haplotype map using QGIS. There are different ways to do this. This way is a bit hacky, but I liked the result compared to the alternatives I tried in QGIS and other software. The result is a haplotype map with individuals coloured by clade, and clustered. This lets you represent clusters using pie charts, where the size is relative to the total number of individuals at that cluster, and the colours of the pie correspond to your different clades:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raven Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/raven-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/raven-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>See the below gist example of my .ahk file to provide shortcuts to Raven. When I started using Raven, version 1.5 did not have shortcuts available. Shortcut support is improving and there are some built in shortcuts. Therefore, you may have no need for this solution, but I liked setting my own shortcut keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split WAVE audio based on selection table</title>
      <link>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/split-raven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/split-raven/</guid>
      <description>Andrew Schwenke 29 October 2022
This is a small example workflow using the warbleR and Rraven packages. It takes a WAVE file and Raven selection table as input, and returns one WAVE file (.wav) for each selection, as well as one Raven selection table (.txt file) per selection. The practice data (CC1_20171010_125500.wav) is an audio recording taken at Cedar Creek, south-east Queensland, Australia, and released by Andrew Schwenke under a CC BY 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variation in _L. wilcoxii_ and _L. jungguy_ advertisement calls: a bioacoustic analysis </title>
      <link>https://andrew-1234.github.io/past-projects/calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrew-1234.github.io/past-projects/calls/</guid>
      <description>There should have been a video here but your browser does not seem to support it. Scrolling spectrogram of a L. wilcoxii from Cedar Creek in south-east Queensland. Made using the dynaSpec package in R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workflow to access and format A20 metadata with R</title>
      <link>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/a2o-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrew-1234.github.io/posts/a2o-api/</guid>
      <description>Andrew Schwenke 24/10/2022
License This repository is licensed under an MIT license. The final hoot detective data set (output/hoot_final.csv) is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License and is attributed to QUT Ecoacoustics and Hoot Detective.
Introduction This is a simple workflow for preparing a dataset that can be used for species distribution modelling, using data from the Hoot Detective project. Hoot Detective is a citizen science project that uses audio from the Australian Acoustic Observatory (A2O).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
